Nathanael Greene Papers 1777-1780 Mss.B.G83
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Miscellaneous Papers, 1777-1780; 0.25 lin. feet
  - Currency, 1776; 1p.; Misc. (Box 8)
    One-third of a dollar note
    vii, 2
  - Currency, 1776; 1p.; Misc. (Box 8)
    Two dollar note
    vii, 3
  - Currency, 1778; 1p.; Misc. (Box 8)
    Seven dollar note
    vii, 4
  - Currency, 1779; 1p.; Misc. (Box 8)
    Three Dollar note
    vii, 5
  - Memorandum, 1779 April; 1p.; Mitchell, John (Box 8)
    Memorandum of sundry articles, received from Col. Mitchell, to be deposited at Estherton, etc.
    xi, 72
  - Account, n.d.; 1p.; Mitchell, John (Box 8)
    Account of clothing sent from the Deputy Quartermaster-General's stores in Philadelphia to the Quartermaster-General's stores at camp in August and September, 1778.
    xi, 48
  - Account, n.d.; 1p.; Mitchell, John (Box 8)
    An account of stores sent to the Quartermaster-General's stores at camp in May and June, 1779.
    iv, 116
  - Memorandum, 1779 March 18; 1p.; Morgan, John (Box 8)
    Memorandum for Gen. Greene concerning the water-carriage on the Potomac.
    xi, 83
  - Miscellaneous list, 1778 December 7; 1p.; Myer, John (Box 8)
    List of provisions and stores remaining at Daniel Wright's.
    x, 32
  - Act and Resolution, 5pp.; New York, State of (Box 8)
    An act to amend an act for regulating impresses of forage and carriages, and for billeting troops within the State of New York.
    iv, 59, 57
  - Receipt, 1779 February 2; 1p.; Opdycke, Joshua (Box 8)
    Receipt for articles delivered by Mr. Mitchell. Signed by Joshua Opdycke.
    x, 88
  - Memorandum, 1779 February 27; 1p.; Otis, Samuel Allyne, 1740-1814 (Box 8)
    Memorandum of money distributed in Quartermaster-General's department.
    x, 85
  - Invoice, 1779 May 8; 1p.; Otis and Henley (Box 8)
    Invoice of woolens purchased and forwarded to William Smith, Esq., at Springfield.
    vii, 63
  - Inventory, 1778 May 28; 1p.; Patton, Robert (Box 8)
    Lebanon - Inventory of horses, etc., sent to Col. Pettit at Moore Hall by Gen. Robert Patton.
    xi, 74
  - Report, n.d.; 5pp.; Plan of March (Box 8)
    Route for Col. Clark's Brigade, from New Windsor to Charlestown, S.C.
    iv, 22, 22a, 23, 24, 25
  - to the Honorable Council of the State of Massachusetts Bay, 1778 August 31; 8pp.; Pynchon, William and other Representatives of the Selectmen of Springfield (Box 8)
    Want of economy in the expenditure of public money destroys the people's confidence. The case of the Continental Ferry across the Connecticut river; the tremendous cost of it; asks that a public inquiry may be made into the matter.
    xi, 90
  - Journal, 1776 May - July; 10pp.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Copy of a journal, covering the months of May and June, 1776, kept by Jacob Shallus, Esq., of Philadelphia, who went upon the expedition to Canada as a volunteer.
    vii, 8
  - Account, 1777 February 20; 5pp.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Lancaster - Account of provisions issued by Jacob Shallus, Deputy Commissary-General.
    vii, 10
  - Oath of allegiance, 1777 September 15; 1p.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Lancaster - Oaths of allegiance to the thirteen United States of America by Jacob Shallus, Commissary of Issues.
    vii, 6
  - Invoice, 1777 November 11; 1p.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Invoice of flour sold at the Continental stores.
    vii, 12
  - Account, n.d.; 4pp.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Account of moneys laid out by Jacob Shallus, Quartermaster to the 1st Pennsylvania Regiment of Foot, commanded by John Philip de Hass, colonel of said regiment, on their march from Philadelphia to Albany, January to September, 1779.
    vii, 11
  - Account, n.d.; 9pp.; Shallus, Jacob (Box 8)
    Account of sundry Continental stores received and delivered at Lancaster.
    vii, 14
  - Estimate, 1779 January 20; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 8)
    Estimate of work for a row-galley.
    xi, 86
  - Estimate, 1779 January 20; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 8)
    Estimate of articles necessary to build a row-galley.
    xi, 87
  - Estimate, 1779 April 9; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 8)
    Fishkill - Estimate of prices for teaming in the State of New York.
    xii, 27
  - Estimate, 1779 May 9; 1p.; Smith, William (Box 8)
    Estimate of the expenses attending certain services to be performed in Department of Springfield.
    iv, 118
  - Account, 1779 July 9; 1p.; Traill, Robert (Box 8)
    Easton - Account of stores and pack-saddles.
    xi, 80
  - to Nathanael Greene, 1779 October 27; 1p.; Van Court, Elias (Box 8)
    Petition from Elias Van Court, a tailor, asking that he may be released from the guard-house, where he has been confined eleven days for some offense.
    viii, 98
  - Muster-roll, 1777 September 17; 1p.; Wagener, Philip (Box 8)
    Capt. Philip Wagener's muster-roll.
    vii, 13
  - Memorandum, 1780 February 14; 1p.; Weiss, Jacob (Box 8)
    Memorandum of espontoons sent to Newburg from June to December, 1779.
    xi, 70
  - Memorandum, 1p.; Weiss, Jacob (Box 8)
    Jacob Weiss' memorandum of clothes at Morristown and Middlebrook.
    x, 34